Guide to the Margaret Taylor Smith Papers, 1918-2010 and undated, bulk 1980-2008 RL.01217
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accessions (2010-0066) and (2010-0135), 1981-1985, 2010, 1 box
  - Transcriptions of interviews, 1983 (Box 33)
  - Profiles for Focal Children, 1983 (Box 33)
  - Accession 2010-0066, email correspondence, 2010 (Box 33)
- Accession (2010-0164), 1970-2009, 1 box
  Acc. (2010-0164) (100 items, 0.2 lin. ft.; dated 1970-2009) includes correspondence regarding the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; the Duke University Women's Studies department; Smith's Class of 1947 and their reunions; and other miscellaneous materials and notes.
  - Duke Reunions Correspondence (Class of 1947), 1970-1997 (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Detroit Medical Center notes, 1997 (Box 34)
  - Women's Health and Wellness Weekend, Duke University, October 2007 (Box 34)
  - General correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 34)
  - Women's Studies Department, Duke University (correspondence, notes, newsletters), 2008-2009 (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Jean O'Barr (correspondence, retirement), 2009 (Box 34)
  - What Does It Mean to be an Educated Women?, Sallie Bingham Center symposium, (correspondence, printed materials, plans), 2009 (Box 34)
- Accession (2011-0077), 1982-2000, 1 box
  Additional material from Margaret Taylor Smith's interviews, research, and correspondence about Mother, I Have Something to Tell You. Also includes copies of some of Smith's talks.
  - Mother, I Have Something to Tell You (Box 35)
    - 3 cassette tapes (Box 35)
    - Agreements and other materials, 1982-1983 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence re: Henry A. Murray Research Center, data, publication, 1983-1984 (Box 35)
  - Talks, 1993-2000, 2 folders (Box 35)